crowdmap.com 2013-01-17

# Crowdmap | Create and Share Interactive Maps Online

## Legal

### Privacy Notice

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for Crowdmap's (the "Crowdmap") website (the "Site"). We reserve the right to modify the information contained herein at anytime without prior notice. If we do make changes to our privacy policies, we will modify this page accordingly. Check this page periodically for amendments. This site and all information and materials on it are provided to you "AS IS" without warranty of any kind.

YOUR USE OF THE SITE, OR YOUR PROVISION TO US OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THESE TERMS AND ANY SUBSEQUENT CHANGES TO THESE TERMS; DO NOT USE THE SITE OR PROVIDE INFORMATION IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS.

#### Normal Browsing

As with many websites, we collect certain information, even when you are not logged in. When you browse, read, or download information from the Site, data is collected by Crowdmap, including but not limited to your IP address, URL request, browser type, and date and time of your request. The data are analyzed in various ways, including using analyzing non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate. We use this information to improve the usefulness of the site to our visitors. Unless you affirmatively provide additional information to us, we do not collect or store personally identifiable information such as name, mailing address, email address, or phone number.

#### Information You Provide

Crowdmap may request personally identifiable information when you register for an account. Information may be used or requested to perform research, improve usability of the site, administer mailing lists or online communities, or other activities related to Crowdmap services. This information may include, but is not limited to, personal names, e-mail addresses, and location.

#### Disclosure of Information

Available log records, account information, and all data stored on our servers may be accessed by our system administrators. In the event that we are required by law (including a court order) to disclose the information you submit, we will provide you with notice (unless we are prohibited) that a request for your information has been made so that you may object to the disclosure. We will send this notice by email to the address you have given us. If you do not challenge the disclosure request yourself, we may be legally required to turn over your information.

#### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that the Site can send to your browser for storage on your computer's hard drive. They make your use of the Site easier by saving your status and preferences and are refreshed every time you visit. We may use session cookies when you visit our website while your browser is open, or while you are logged into the Site. To facilitate our registration and login functions, we may use cookies to recognize when you return to the Site. If you do not logout of your account, these cookies allow us to keep track of your username and password so that you do not have to resubmit the information to log into your account. If others will be using your computer, you should log out of your account so that your logon information is cleared. Most browser are initially set to accept cookies, but you may be able to change the settings to refuse cookies or to be alerted when cookies are being sent.

#### Children's Privacy

The Site's content is intended for adults and we will not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a child under age 13 who you believe has submitted personal information to the Site, please contact us immediately.

#### Posting

Posting or updating content on the Site is a public action, and all content may be publicly visible. Identification of all contributed content may include, but is not limited to, display of your account name or IP address. All content may be retained for restorative, archival, or research purposes by Crowdmap. Editing or deleting content may alter the displayed state of the content, but will not permanently delete the content from the Site.

#### Security

The Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, your confidential use of the Site cannot be guaranteed by Crowdmap. Crowdmap shall not be responsible for any harm that you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality in respect to your use of this Site or any information you transmitted to the Site.

#### Other Websites

Material on this website may link to independently run websites outside of the Crowdmap domain. Crowdmap is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of any websites you visit from this website.
